yesterday of the day before I promised
to cover the four powers are genuine
tear from attic over los cuatro Polaris
it's part of it's hard to get rid of a
negative karma company
come on disassembles Ilona don't a
semi get negative at a karma and it's
part of we teaching in DC on level one
illa cinemas and they say no man evil Oh
No so I've done it like a hundred times
in the last few years
Rachael siento services and also two
messiahs so I have a good spiel okay
does that number in this course oh and
by the way whoever arranged the churros
thank you very much tokine organ it's
almost two rows muchas gracias
[Music]
there's a churro shop in Beijing I own a
team they chose in Beijing but there's
nothing like a guava heart you know when
I chose Iguala all right here we go
so we teach this thing I all over all
over the world
estamos de ser el redoble we teach
people that the pan is coming from the
seeds in their mind that way if you are
new let us see how much a la gente que
las casas businesses maybe if you have a
phone with lots of space to see so no
sitting no telephone no Congress Bastian
I'll do like 12 or 15 minutes under for
Paris oh yeah awesome minutos de los
cuatro Polaris so if you don't know them
well he knows a lot of ambien make a
recording grab and low and I'll drink a
coffee you Maria to my own cafe if you
want to put it up into camp on the rocky
su Solaris I'll give you the classic
presentation as well a presentation
Classica
and I won't do it again in a lawyer boy
evaluator self unless I do I mean a
sketchy lawyer
vamos vamos vamos
okay let's go so after you teach the pen
and say your you are all gonna be a CIT
teacher dos - MS was the ACI and after
you teach the perilous presence in la
pluma you have to teach the first thing
casanare los cuatro pesos then wait 24
hours this person's been in seventy
cuatro horas and the most intelligent
people in the room Heelys personas mass
intelligent en el cuarto they will start
coming to you the new people lost knows
when they pass away need yes so like the
pair it is inertia yesterday la pluma
coming from sees in my mind in a
seminary maintained so that means
significant people I know are coming
from las personas que conozco being in
the semi just yeah see and my business I
mean they were shootin min yeah in my
body
you mean cuerpo yeah ok ok I got it I'm
gonna make good sealant in the way plant
I wanna see me yes 24 hours later even
the cuatro horas después if they it's
almost an IQ test as Cascione primarily
qu the certain percentage i guess about
50 percent rocky common king's por
ciento that same people will come after
24 hours as me must promote husband in
las mismas personas been indisposed
event de cuatro horas is there some way
to like you know cancel the vatican
solaris - it's amazing all over the
world doesn't matter what country it's
in clear Lisa % Armando's in important
Pais you know about 48 hours after they
hear the pin for each other the specific
escucha la pluma
the more intelligent people las personas
mass intelligent and what they're really
saying is look astonishing don't rely
that is I understand I
can now design the rest of my life
in Teaneck Apolo dicen el resto de mi
vida and I'm ready to do it
yes sir listo para said lo but what
about all the crappy seeds I made before
I met the pan ok pass I like controller
samia's my last kiss until the escuchar
you know what's the official policy
Laura Clementis of the cialis can you
just cancel them castle of sports cancel
our then then you have to say no you
have to learn the four powers caponord
los cuatro polaris so I'm going to do
the four powers there's more yesterday's
Quattro Polaris and we might go a little
bit over time okay kiddo starting on
some Pokemon I also won't tell long
stories because you're trying to record
it for a couple question and he started
like Aspergillus Taliban but I'll tell
some shorter stories basically story is
my score okay so Buddha wrote a Sutra
Buddha spoken Sutra Buddha oblong Sutra
called chapter Bala Sutra chapter
rubella so Chuck Chuck tooth means for
tattoo significant Quattro and when it
comes before a or be like chaturanga
the enters the veneer they awake or
chaturanga the s change to our ok nice
is a come then bottom means power
balance and recap over okay so and it's
the root of the English word for for the
rise de la palabra in english jano for
which is the root of the word for poor
like Singapore case the pajamas in the
polo Jaipur okay okay so anyway for
general so so I think the first thing
when you're teaching it la primera cosa
kisses I think it's important to put it
into the Buddha's mouth it's it's
penelon local le bouton so this is not
something made up by Tibetan it sooner
San Lucas inventory this is this is the
real thing it's just like oh sorry Alice
this is a method for dealing with Bad
Seeds it's assumed metal paralegal
Kamala simmias which was taught directly
by the SNL directamente para war so I
think first it's important to establish
the
the ability cookie promotes important
establish a clear they believe that
so four powers just means four steps to
to stop the power of a negative seen
those quadrupolar a significant cuatro
pesos preliminary poder de estas -
images and we could call it the four
steps but then I'll get confused with
the four steps before - cuatro passes
per second area nosotros
cuatro pesos so we call it for powers -
lemons los cuatro poder is why are they
powers porque su Polaris they have the
power to stop the power of a bad seed
por que tener poder de tener el poder de
stress - images so if you know how to
stop the power of your bad season if you
know how to plant good seeds there's no
reason why you shouldn't have a perfect
year tone si puedes planter esto los
restos cuatro pathos para eliminar el
poder de las fallas Amyas y los cuatro
Passos para plant are located
no I problema de una Buena Vida I knew
then in my own life mi vida when I was
in college on the star in la Isla I got
a girl pregnant and but it's in that
shower she was she said she was on birth
control
yahiko que estaba tomando and my college
professors the concept is they and my
high school teachers in is mystras they
all said abortion is okay they can kill
our son has to have in and I was gone in
in India we study just I'm in India and
the woman decide to have an abortion
yes tomorrow decidió tener una Wharton
and she wrote me and I kind of wrote
back very slow we miss kvie material
respond there so I wouldn't have it
wouldn't be on me working over a me
culpa so really it is on me we're at sea
and she had an abortion
yeah yeah Porto and then I I just went
on with my life yes oh no continued
economy and then when I met my
rude mnemonic honestly I'm Ilana rice
you know I told him about it
latias it's like you need the four
powers man mr. los cuatro Polaris I'm
like okay teach me the four powers to
warrant Cinderella Zoe
so here's the four powers number one
primero
it's called tangy top which means the
foundation power a cell phone el poder
elephant fundamental and go back to the
foundation of your understand regressive
tell fundamental that they los antennae
Mientus and the pail is a perfect place
to go to La Paloma Sal you are perfect
okay so just say I'm gonna do power
number one we shall put America there
and sit down with a pen you know into
the corner Paloma yeah just think about
it for half an hour it's been said cerca
de esto por meliora and that's the first
power that's just simply my father go
back to your roots better Ella rice
which is the pen la pluma now if you
really understand the pen st. endemic
Roman clearly that you understand that
when you when you say something like I'm
not stupid you stupid name was kept
cuando tienes algo como yo no soy stupid
Tauruses to peel are you the stupidest
kids in college who knows New Year's
message to pedasi guadalajara when those
words come to your ear converses Pilar
Sal Cassano so so Eidos
then they make an impression on your
mind as an impression and Ostrom
maintain and that becomes a seed yes a
committee known as a media and that
doubles in power every 24 hours
yesterday's applicant poetically in the
cuatro horas so the second power is a
wonderful air it's like I gotta take
care of this thing you can carry a vase
you could do to the top it means oh my
god I gotta take care of this thing it
was mere matter okay cyclist and
I gotta do it get it yeah okay so it's
the decision
it's another session I gotta take care
of this thing now I'm eating okay so the
categories to order okay
and and don't wait a week or three days
cuz it's six times stronger it's 12
times stronger don't don't wait no
suspend a semi not really a sport case a
so those bases must poderoso
no a spelling use use it use it was a no
lower Louisville you know it's a sense
of urgency it didn't to do
Connor hint I should I should take care
of this seat now but don't kiss our
cargo disgusting me yeah alright take
this C down no nothing will get a car
our then the third power will stay set
for there is it this is a negative
decision soon a soon I wanna
decision negativa I will not do this
again the warrior will get us arrest and
you know when you're teaching it
condolences in siendo tell people the
yellow country if you can't remember all
four see not the postcode are los cuatro
just remember number three equality
Delano mattress because in English we
say number three does all the heavy
lifting
no me no trace si todo el trabajo que
power number three is the real power
it's a silver dollar of power and it's
the decision not to do it again
que la decisión didn't know what where
recession that that's the one that
really hurts the bad see it's just like
a relevant a year Li my last media ok so
then in the next breath and that's an
American expression also in the next
breath and siente sospiro
say gonna you should say there is a race
here look there's certain bad deeds that
you can't promise for the rest of your
life you won't do it I CSS - actions can
a post-prom at their candle as possible
whereas airport arrested to via an
abortion is kind of clear and easy
Ella were to see a salvo fastening
Eclair
okay I won't have an abortion again in
my life I'm miles away whatever send me
Vida you could for example you could
become a monk and say I won't have sex
in my life so no abortions for example
the post commercial no movies no way
vulgar at intersections por lo tanto no
way to narrow or toes so it's possible
to make a commitment that you're not
going to do something again it's
possible acestus aesthetically
compromises can all of us about what I
said but some some negative deeds
mycosis negated section is negative us
well like okay
one of my worst negative deeds or Hebrew
name is Paris action is malice it's
feeling jealous or competitive of other
teachers a scintilla missile also or fan
scented competencia the others Macondo
chose my drives my memorization of
Scripture it's just look at me so
Maurice ask it to us okay I'm just being
honest
so I remember you know I've been
fighting this one for my whole life
creo que esta hablando con éxito la
Movida so I remember I was I was in
meditation in New Jersey 30 years ago
mokou Lucas a trained tenure system a
tendon over Jersey and I'm like I'm
gonna clean this seat because I'm
jealous of my teachers other good
student investors I mean yeah poor
Kasturi shallow so al otro estudiante
minimized
who translated a book called the
operation in your hands if I do only you
know Casey generally whereas Fernando's
- okay and then I'm like that's really
bad and I'm jealous
smooth Milo Costello so let's do the
four-part like I said a spotter
operators number one no matter all no
okay remember the pen record a diploma
if you're jealous you're just gonna your
own intelligence will get left she is
sitting the sailors to intelligences
about this mean wish if you're jealous
of someone else's intelligence your own
intelligence what job
sister Stella civilian must be
Intelligencia say reduce okay I got that
okay yellow tang was the power number
two port number of those I've been
jealous of him for years the Neo Salah
sister persona perennials
it's it's gonna increase the seeds are
multiplying every 24 hours
yes - by chrysella semester multiplicand
Ocala veinticuatro all's I have to do
something then we'll kiss Adele go it's
called also called gear pick top regret
I'm sorry I did that
let me see I'm a cupid talk it's lotion
Shindo cases it's a bad idea
mera Pinto then number three numero tres
I won't do it again
no no one will read a cell then I mean I
distinctly remembered the mental
conversation make weirdo move a specific
comment to them in conversation mentally
I won't do it again no lo voy a hacer do
one hacer can be jealous of art the
nurse a lost a heart jealous of iron
salut salut so the art yeah eh eh eh
like him more than me see a rainbow
jelly chemical cami that's so irritating
es muy Dante you know I remember
breaking the vow while I'm while I'm
fixing it clearly pasa
you are breaking in it you're not
supposed to do it again in your life
you're breaking it in the same manner
cannot escape let us say a lot of
messages in Alameda Supra Regalado so
when you teach condolence a nice power
number 3 el poder numero tres there's a
tradition a unit tradición up the llamas
de los llamas and there's a you're
supposed to tell your students it was a
serial - sis - the antes set a
reasonable time limit bounine
you know fecha límite personally like
decide you're not going to be jealous of
art the silicon I was at the nurse'll oh
the art immediately start eating a
churro
inmediatamente committing to roll your
focus will be on the children they focus
on a churro and tell the end of this
churro
just elfin eldest a churro I won't be
jealous of our
no one else is in there are really
focused on the children
I forgot emotional children okay I
understand if you're your husband's
great ánotá spa so make a promise as
soon a professor I won't miss pasa por
cuatro Diaz then come to the long memory
know mentality of the lamrim
and make sure not to recharge your phone
yes cigarette there is no cargo to
telephone oh I understand
okay then so start at time on tiempo big
things like I cheated on my taxes cosas
como hacer trample awesome points can
stay in my lifetime I won't do it again
what is hidden all the way what we're
selling maybe the abortion abortion but
the mental or traumas those make Karma's
mentalis in American English they say
it's like trying to catch a small pig
which has grease on its body
Eskimo tatar they they said of kissing
wrassle so ok so make a reasonable time
in opponent impo limited as finale
that's a negative commitment compromise
on negativo I won't do it again for 30
seconds nobody has had portentous a
wound also then number 4 numero Quatro
is a positive committee as a compromise
a positive way to balance that karma
para balance the Karma I would do
different camera please algo diferente
so I asked my teacher in the case of my
abortion levanta me my son el caso de
aborto
what what can I do to balance it que
pasa para balance hello and he said
started children's program completion
program opera Nino's teach Dharma to
children it's a nearly that man was
named because you kill the child
forget to my testimony continue the
theme can be the same time apostles
similar ok so I say ok I'll start a
children's okay when you present program
para ninos
and then I ask him how long it's going
to take the quanto tempo what amar you
know
until the seat is finished then I'm like
yeah I know but see you're saying how
long is that 113 possess so and there
are you have to keep doing it and so
it's not something you can do once no
successful una vez
you know you don't do this one you do it
every day no losses solo never lost or
loss yes you recommit to your negative
promise I won't do it again
well this a compliment Eric honest
promise and negativa Kanaloa Solverson
you recommit to your positive promise I
mean then compromiso positivo until you
get a clear sign that the seed is killed
a second thing as soon as an elk glad I
get to see media for this through even
now it gets interesting
yes to link to the Sun are you guys okay
to go over time ence los perros
Alchemist maybe we'll start the next
class a little later okay I someone
Lucinda class I almost started a ok so
to understand the how long it's gonna
take my intended quanto tempo what
tomorrow you have to understand what the
goal really is
they almost intended koalas are made
them really that what's the third law of
karma quit litter CLE de l'académie
sorry fourth la la cuarta little Karma
if you do something Jesse salgo you must
get a result yeah there was a tener el
resultado and if someone could give you
what you call exception Caliente para
una opción
Oh Baba all your good states will open
and all your bad seas will disappear ok
that's just when assumed years whenever
he told us my lesson will disappear why
that is why I said that's not right it's
almost being ok gravity says they're
gonna be that be see if the earth is
bigger than the pennant
let go of the pencil a tear as
mechanical a plume of oil aroma pen will
falter la pluma silica aerosol a tiara
okay that's just gravity
it's just gotta be that if someone could
give you an exception salient a other
interception random exceptions on the
Saturnalia Toria then car cars on the
highway would fall into the sky every
once in a while and everything cuando
los carros a people would get rewards
you can't in my wallet andrea
recompenses so one of the most
comforting things about the universe una
de las casas Mezrich important is a
universal is that if you really
understand karma with cashier element
and emotion karma the universe is
predictable is facil para serial
universe it makes sense thinnest until
it's not chaos noise cows now our if you
could hurt people
si podemos a little hint if you could
kill babies in abortions support a
Muslim at our babies and nothing happens
to you in not a person Allah then you
could do lots of good comments and
nothing good come to you also
esta bien para ser Boros Karma's you can
have whatever anger understand so then
demos I I think if you ask me my
preference see me see my pramantha me
preference yeah I would rather have a
universe where there are some rules
administrative only verses on there a
class just a Regulus if you help someone
you get something good seen a us a
little tear someone else will tell if
you hurt someone you get something bad
you see Daniel salient is Omar Kazuto
can you imagine if it was not that way
say point imagine a scene no further
scene so I have a small cafe in my town
they don't pequeña cafe my Pueblo it's
the only cafe in within an hour
a salut Nicole cafe kala una hora okay I
went there recently
why a resentiment a oh by the way it's
really fun to go there or sister smooth
every day they close at two o'clock or
Sirena last
forget about translating a book there
would be the human Leroy and and all the
Cowboys come and all the old people come
it's a hangout for the whole community
even Antonio rancheros closby hito
system where para poner take they're all
like really really country people yes
can't a little Campo del mental Jeff
como estas
what would you plant this year different
pastor Stan you planted the 20s and the
years watermelons
sandy years and they talk like that
whole day yes it actually drive it
craziness here not only at the local
because gia is on the other side of the
cafe with the Jada style a lot of
Louisville cafe so once again he twisted
oh I got bananas three bananas Platanos
oh you don't plan it sandy and you got
Platina platinum planters and yes
twister Platanos yeah it's a real mess
serious in the sastra the whole field
covered with all bananas told me Campo
created a black penis I'm going bankrupt
student Camerata can you imagine a
conversation like that super machine
there is the conversation if Sandhya
don't make Sandhya sillas MVNOs una
sandía
the world would be chaos in motion cows
by the way I'm buying this cafe forces
the circumference to talk next week the
scientist a man cuz they retired
orchestrated our own Jed retired yet
separate it all I said you can't retire
it is I'm tired
Nadia you don't sell to compress then I
thought why no no a comprar because
otherwise the people don't have any
place to go in one hours you know la
gente que no tiene el Don the ear so me
and Veronica gonna buy it
nobody else can I run it O'Malley manova
and but she asked me on the telephone
yesterday I am a medium or Jerry may
prevent oh please ask the people in the
retreat to give you papers with
suggestions for the name of the new name
of the Cafe de las personas del retiro
Camden
so here inches the nombre del cafe okay
right now the name is cricket's little
nombre is cricket's previous creole
bridges
yeah and the owner said you cannot have
the name you make enough points then
there's the nombre okay okay okay so
anyway imagine if you go to crystal
clear imagine imagine and secure an
egregious or whatever you choose the
name or location hombre and and the
farmers are talking your son Landon was
growing heroes what do you play
capelin dusty water mill Sandhya's what
you get you get to waste it banana
Latinos they all spoil in one day Josefa
here in the non dia okay so I think it's
better that the universe has some basic
rules do cookies bueno que el universo
thing as shelter fellas basic if you
heard people CLS's annual gain something
burn had an algo mal tell a person if
you help people she led us and again
something good happen tell gobo no
therapist then we can deal with life yes
he podemos UDL con la Vida life is you
know we're stupid but if we work hard we
can make a nice life so most don't owe
specific trauma Hamas being the person I
went a vida
so it's actually not possible
no it's possibly to kill about my
paranormal as familia if it was possible
she for a possibly then it would be
possible to serve other people and bad
things happen to you say that
possibility we don't trust personas he
knows passing my las casas understand
intending we gotta have rules here they
almost certainly Regulus they can't
apply to half of the seas and not apply
to the other half Latino cone applicator
lammeter las semillas paranoia so trauma
and loss and it's gravely yes graviton
it's the way it is
yes you can't just cancel about the no
post implemented cancel anomalous
Familia you cannot take it out on the
post Sokka it's gonna stay there and
tell it open so I can i yes take a
shower
so geshe-la why do the four powers
occasionally just by like a circus
cuatro politics
how the four powers works Combusken
functional squad now listen this is
crucial
it's just crucial and I'm taking my nap
time right now yeah with the system and
me
import system for this important if you
have a watermelon seed una semilla
Sandia and you plant it you LaPlante us
and you in the spring in la primavera
and you put water philoponus agua you
will get a Big Sandy area Grande 3/4 and
d3 so Quatro say yes but if you put a
watermelon seed here persepolis last
minute sandy rocky and you keep it warm
illa materials come Cologne and you put
water lily pond ozawa it will try to
open but Saturday Arif it will split and
sprout will come out una pequeña by
Posada Academy enough and then it will
die because there's no supporting
conditions is a lot more important like
conditions Kahlo support there's not
enough Stan I know suficiente loose
there's not enough soil
nice efficient a tiara okay it will try
to open but at a debrief so the this
amazing technique is a technical
incredibly I'm stopping bad seeds for a
Paris Amelia's malice is trying to
trigger a premature birth it's a circus
as I said with it's okay demented solo
consuming yes garlic and tendon just
with soul unless I mean just with bad
see so look at - Amy okay so you tried
to figure it was just attended a hacer
premature birth que la Samia surrender
merriment the way you destroy a seed
with the four powers is
you don't destroy it illa Foreman K this
treasonous americano squatter polarizes
can only destroy us if you did then
watermelon seeds would make bananas CC
entonces la Samir's a this and the idea
and Platanos so you just try to make it
open to su su elementalists camera and
this okay and and where does this
teaching come from they don't know me
instance indians for $300 the three
centers already know older students no
no no system losses to enters and he was
no point i see another one two three
okay
where did cancel cancel cancel out it's
too much money which I never had you
already know okay so a mantis now it
says D Singh the seed will open to kill
SMEs have a rhythm with temprano and a
person who was supposed to die of cancer
will have an unusual migraine for one
day unit persona que se supone que tenia
que more ear the cancel button Eminem a
granny put on the a person who was
supposed to die of cancer I think a
satanic a morir the cancer will have an
unusual migraine for one day Martin
arrow button on a migraine you know
swell poor india so and I asked my
number
canola plume Tammy llama how long's I
got it have a kids class
quanto tempo tengo que tener is the
classifier los ninos to make the
abortion see stop I kissed a semi yeah
they were to say he's like you don't
make the abortion seed stock which is no
normal opposed to circuit party you make
it open to early as cassava
prima tournament yeah how do you make it
open to early Hamas as cassava antes
do some balance come assume karma para
balance you promise not to do it again
promoters noble fellow said does step
three step four powerful powerful Tracy
Quattro would then I'm like how do you
know the bad series opened you know too
early commercial scale SMEs everyo muy
temprano
he said there's two sides I don't sing
so this I'm giving you the two sides
Lester gondolas OC I finished the four
powers tetrominos Quattro passes I'm
giving you the
since this is - then don't lose those
signals how you know when to stop the
common sense porno the hell that says
quadrupoles you can predict the answer
was Priscilla la respuesta you will have
a small intense unusual mess up in your
life problem a pic can you intend so II
I almost Santino I almost said not I
almost didn't say mess up I almost said
something else
no hay problema de algo mas you will
have some small intense short disaster
I'll go korto intense and it's it's
usually like one day or something so
momentous on the air well listen in
intense intense migraine that you never
felt in your whole life una millennium
win 10 sake Hamas a listen to you is a
is typical its algo typical or after
owning the same car for 10 years and you
never had a scratch on it
this positon el mismo carro or this I
know she Hamas you're registered you
come out of the grocery store and it's
all smashed and the person went already
salads they let the been super is the
complete a mentalist Rosa so Buddhist
reaction to a small intense disaster
direction they emboldened the staff you
[Music]
can assess yourself then I got
suspicious of my llama you know it just
to be not so special Camille Emma and I
asked a very important question upon the
muy importante
how do you know that's not just a bad
seed opening Kamala diferencia or comas
Ava's castanos simplement anomalous
Amelia Cabrillo from scratching
someone's card before and it's not
connected to the abort the Venera
carro de alguien que no está connected
Oh al abort oh you you seem to have an
answer but it's a key didn't let exposed
yeah yeah yeah so I'll give a this is
how I teaching in DC as you can see nice
and easy I had this backpack tengo esta
mochila it weighs about 20 kilos it's a
como bean turkey looks every year it
weighs more or else I'm feeling older I
don't know pessimist animals be okay I
find more stuff too it's my office
it's just me oficina I was in Beijing s
table in Beijing I went to visit the
guy's office where we start level she's
not even a person said this office cost
me five million dollars u.s. rent per
year maybe her stop wishing them a
question comedians $1 the rental on you
and that table cost 1 million dollars
just a mess Acosta antique you know so
don't take without then I'm like yeah ok
ok then he said you want to see my house
also that main kid is wearing me casa
and I'm like in my mind I'm like no you
may meet a star yeah let's go see you
almost hardly instead we can walk to
your to my house almost come in enemy
Casa I'm like yeah ok bueno
my translation for the day is
disappearing jam it took shown the div
that I'm like okay
bueno then we went past Starbucks but
someone was started and I said stop the
pilot he said were like ok I say this is
my author s s miovision I have one in
every city they're gonna and told us you
Alice why cuz this is my office
porque poor casters my office in this
but anyways it's heavy
if SL heavy nowadays I have to have
someone like Victor go with me the keys
to killing como Victor of any like cargo
and then me and Veronica went to the
movie even on the Qaddafi masalas she
said it's like a day you know for most I
wanna see we've been dating for this
year is 50 years they're almost just in
Quinton SS Daniels
and so I said you know she said we're
going on a date after 50 years ago by
Masana see today's forum was just some
quaint años I have a question can
request they're gonna the capital okay
can you not bring the bag then I'm like
I have to choose between my bag and my
partner you know he's behind me mochila
enter me in my panic okay okay then I
remember we got out of the car in Sedona
to go see the movie
II make okay no salimos del carro and
Sedona payaso like a superhero
hey good machine to super he has its cuz
you don't have the backpack
opportunities to achieve my yoga yes
could you pick it up on edge oh no it's
because you're not carrying the backpack
no it's poor canastas car not too
mochila why are we talking about
porque estamos hablando resto that as
north
that's another famous sign Kamala Khan
Orestes autre senior from other cities
finished case Jessica Walla and la
semilla
you wake up in the morning the spirits
in the manana you have an unusual joy in
your heart you can say Allah grant in
your swollen tu corazon you feel like
you just took off a backpack that you
are carrying for 10 years
yokas como que tu casa que una mochila
que Dios cargando design news yeah so
those two signs it's to those signals
number one no Moroni you have a small
intense disaster in the sastra Peck can
you intend so so how do you know it's
just not a normal disaster ecchymosis
can resume normal disaster normal then
after that you feel like the supposed
SOT scientists
I feel something different it's
inter-cell Cal go study for anything
together
okay got it until now I'll tell you a
cool story especially a story a movie
which I'm not supposed to do cuz we're
way over time exponent you know they'll
take half an hour after evening traffic
a sake tell me
okay come on mo man I got a email from a
lady named Adele nunca rail in
California Bruna personal in Colleen's
reported she owns a Volkswagen bus it a
name una combi well you know what's the
opposite of appetito come being coffee
combi copy calmly combi I'm stinking
okay
and I was driving down the highway he
mejor que estaba I'm an economist if it
cost highway it goes next to the ocean
Carol Pacific it's a very nice drive but
it's very beautiful my simple Perez mas
Atomos you get to watch the ocean porque
es el océano and and I was listening to
your she has a CD player you make okay
just a scooch endo and on CD so I was
listening to you teach the four powers
easy hairstyles could channel when I was
young two years he never lost Quattro
Polaris and then I thought well you said
what's the second time the Pensacola
salsa when the polar regret but it means
there's a Pinto producing if he had care
of it today
take care of it now as a cargo order
because it's growing like cancer because
the casino coming so she said I had an
inspiration
dijo turbulence pedestrian I will do the
for powers right now right here while
he's talking on the city was caught
reporters or eat amis mom interest and
honesty so she's like okay I have this
bad a goes to my love it though I
won't do it again for three days no no
whatever I say reporters yes I will try
to make up for that are they the
compañero and then her car burst into
flames you su carro the repent ascension
deposition yeah the whole combo is
burning for lecomba sister came and and
she said she'd jump out she pulled over
she jump amigo que estas en I say
mistletoe and policemen come in
la policia and they think she's crazy
person okay star loca because she's
going don't you know my brother it can
be secure the policeman thing she's like
insane
the police ship and Sokka style off and
what's the last line on her email from
the Ultima flashings who email send me a
new cd-rom over monomino CD it got
burned up in the car or case I came home
and I thought oh really okay cool and
save you so that's I think I thought did
I cover everything I told you say
cabrito oh one more thing
which I like to talk about what we did
yeah we did one more thing una cosa mas
there's a custom in Catholicism in a
costume Brunell cattle is the final
after Isis bomb in the religion of
Mexico everything under Mexico there's
when you teach and you have a translator
you have to use you try one word and
then you quite a solicitation trattoria
Nintendo's console you know it does cos
there's a very beautiful custom called
final last rites last last rites final
prayers a Unitarian Cosima Santos Oh
Leo's yeah
Oh Leo's
Santos Oh Leo's Santa's all yours holy
Oreos yeah
Santos all lives so and you take the
person's confession if toma de
convención de una persona just before
they die until the case of Merlin so
really data for pars that meant the esos
quadrupoles if the person honestly admit
they made a mistake selection Terrell
meant a admit a kiss on their or it's
gonna help them a lot that's bad yo that
mojo so it's a very very pure and a good
custom assume that costume well good I
wanna you know then I remember my father
was very ill with cancer recurred okay
me peritoneal cancer just ammonium Fermo
he's gonna die in a week in a stop one
to the more sinister
I went to him stay with him help him to
free a Claire McInerney I do very low he
couldn't eat food for the camara so I
just make orange juice cinemas who we
watch football games all day he way most
part it was a football tool because he
doesn't believe in anything
no kind nada and then I'm thinking just
happens and he's he's gonna die so a
motive and he killed a lot of people in
the world war 2 y el macho macho gente
la segunda Garmin daily he was on a
summary esta bueno Submarino and his job
su trabajo is the machine gun on the top
of the staircase Augusto Riva del Sol
Moreno and they never use it
I'm at Lawson cuz they're on the water
Pakistan baccala but when you think
another ship or cuando nosotros
there will be a thousand men in the
water Emile personas en el agua and you
come up and you shoot them eat the salad
she loves lettuce Paris so you killed
you murdered them they are hopeless
helpless and you kill them one by one
no Tina says no tienen Esperanza los
matazano so they cannot fight again but
I cannot put my weight up earlier so
that was his job
SSO trauma and he was 17 years old
quaternary siete honest so if we you
know and then some thinking how to get
him to confess cuz he doesn't believe in
Buddha or Jesus just happens and the
commercial okay confesses porque no
clean and Bernie his sous some like I
had an idea in store in a then I sat
down next to him is in the control I
give him an orange cheese who was
another huh
and I said dad you know you never ever
he talked about the war once in love
Lord and the la coruna was the night my
brother committed suicide not checking
me hermano sister says oh he found my
brother a link on camera and he got very
drunk you seen more nacho he remembered
the bloodshed you say : no start to talk
about it because wobbler a video so that
I said you remember you told me about
shooting all those guys in the required
the coolest konami history ladies
parasitosis yeah I remember I told you
see microcut a big dinner okay this is
called
upaya what this means by occur
significant taco this glucose spirit
dwell to record spirit well then I'm
like would you do that again today a
castle where yes si estoy no I I will
never do that no how malleable was and
I'm like see understand and tendon so if
someone in your family alguien en su
familia it's very sick
stallion for you see a car accident
somebody's dying open an eccentric rol
guest amore endo try to get these words
I think a just try to get them to say
these canisters palabras no I wouldn't
do that know how Marlo already asserted
then if they die yes you say morning
it's it's very cool okay moving you'd
help them a lot
it was much healthier more cheese so
that's how you can give someone the last
right as soon as ellos no soleus Santos
always yeah so it's a good custom so now
when a customer and you can you can you
can do it yourself the processor to okay
if someone's dying challenging system or
yendo soon grab her pronto talk to them
about the bad things they did in their
life I recently lost my las casas
keychain and so he encouraged them to
say I would not do it again in spirit
knows Acadian canola woman I would
rather say and then that third power is
the main one it's a Tercel Polaris
little principality and they will have a
much better reaper even okay Nona
oh my horrendous amento so try to
encourage people that in the in spirit
loss cool being that's my four powers
take this mix because under the squatter
Polaris what time they're supposed to
start in the evening seven-thirty